buzzbox.com 2010-12-30

# Terms of Service And Privacy Policy

### Terms of Service

By using the BuzzBox.com web site, a service of Buzzbox, Inc., you are agreeing to be bound by the following terms and conditions (“Terms of Use”).  
Basic Terms

  1. You must be 13 years or older to use this site. 
  2. You are responsible for any activity that occurs under your screen name. 
  3. You are responsible for keeping your password secure. 
  4. You must not abuse, harass, threaten, impersonate or intimidate other BuzzBox users. 
  5. You may not use the BuzzBox.com service for any illegal or unauthorized purpose. International users agree to comply with all local laws regarding online conduct and acceptable content. 
  6. You are solely responsible for your conduct and any data, text, information, screen names, graphics, photos, profiles, audio and video clips, links (“Content”) that you submit, post, and display on the BuzzBox.com service. 
  7. You must not modify, adapt or hack BuzzBox.com or modify another website so as to falsely imply that it is associated with BuzzBox.com . 
  8. You must not create or submit unwanted email to any BuzzBox members (“Spam”). 
  9. You must not transmit any worms or viruses or any code of a destructive nature. 
  10. You must not, in the use of BuzzBox, violate any laws in your jurisdiction (including but not limited to copyright laws). 

Violation of any of these agreements will result in the termination of your BuzzBox.com account. While BuzzBox.com prohibits such conduct and content on its site, you understand and agree that BuzzBox cannot be responsible for the Content posted on its web site and you nonetheless may be exposed to such materials and that you use the BuzzBox.com service at your own risk.  
General Conditions

  1. We reserve the right to modify or terminate the BuzzBox.com service for any reason, without notice at any time. 
  2. We reserve the right to alter these Terms of Use at any time. If the alterations constitute a material change to the Terms of Use, we will notify you via internet mail according to the preference expressed on your account. What constitutes a “material change” will be determined at our sole discretion, in good faith and using common sense and reasonable judgement. 
  3. We reserve the right, in accordance with any applicable laws, to refuse service to anyone for any reason at any time. 
  4. We may, but have no obligation to, remove Content and accounts containing Content that we determine in our sole discretion are unlawful, offensive, threatening, libelous, defamatory, obscene or otherwise objectionable or violates any party’s intellectual property or these Terms of Use. 
  5. The BuzzBox service makes it possible to post images and text hosted on BuzzBox to outside websites. This use is accepted (and even encouraged!). However, pages on other websites which display data hosted on BuzzBox.com must provide a link back to BuzzBox. 
  6. We reserve the right to reclaim usernames on behalf of businesses or individuals that hold legal claim or trademark on those usernames. 

Copyright (What’s Yours is Yours)

  1. We claim no intellectual property rights over the material you provide to the BuzzBox service. Your profile and materials uploaded remain yours. You can remove your profile at any time by deleting your account. This will also remove any text and images you have stored in the system. 
  2. We encourage users to contribute their creations to the public domain or consider progressive licensing terms. 
  3. BuzzBox undertakes to obey all relevant copyright laws. We will review all claims of copyright infringement received and remove content deemed to have been posted or distributed in violation of any such laws. To make a claim, please provide us with the following: 
    * A physical or electronic signature of the copyright owner or the person authorized to act on its behalf; 
    * A description of the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed; 
    * A description of the infringing material and information reasonably sufficient to permit BuzzBox to locate the material; 
    * Your contact information, including your address, telephone number, and email; 
    * A statement by you that you have a good faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; and 
    * A statement that the information in the notification is accurate, and, under the pains and penalties of perjury, that you are authorized to act on behalf of the copyright owner. 

Claims can be sent to team@BuzzBox.com. Contact the agent designated to receive and act on copyright violations under the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (DMCA).

(These terms of service were inspired by Flickr & Twitter.)

### Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of Aug 17, 2009.

BuzzBox provides this Privacy Policy to inform users of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personally identifiable information received from users of this website, located at www.buzzbox.com (“Site” ) or collected through our social networking service, including via SMS, WAP and Instant Messaging (“Service” ). This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time for any reason; each version will apply to information collected while it was in place. We will notify you of any material changes to our Privacy Policy by posting the new Privacy Policy on our Site. You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes.

By using our Site you are consenting to our processing of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy now and as amended by us. “Processing” means using cookies on a computer or using or touching information in any way, including, but not limited to, collecting, storing, deleting, using, combining and disclosing information, all of which activities will take place in the United States. If you reside outside the U.S. your personally identifiable information will be transferred to the U.S., and processed and stored there under U.S. privacy standards. By visiting our Site and providing information to us, you consent to such transfer to, and processing in, the US.

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or our use of your personally identifiable information, please contact us at privacy at buzzbox dot com.  
Information Collection and Use

Our primary goals in collecting personally identifiable information are to provide you with the product and services made available through the Site, including, but not limited, to the Service, to communicate with you, and to manage your registered user account, if you have one.

Information Collected Upon Registration. If you desire to have access to certain restricted sections of the Site, you will be required to become a registered user, and to submit certain personally identifiable information to BuzzBox. This happens in a number of instances, such as when you sign up for the Service, or if you desire to receive marketing materials and information. Personally identifiable information that we may collect in such instances may include your IP address, full user name, password, email address, city, time zone, telephone number, and other information that you decide to provide us with, or that you decide to include in your public profile.

Additional Information Your full user name and your photo, if you decide to upload one, are displayed to people in the BuzzBox network to enable you to connect with people on BuzzBox, as specified in your privacy settings. Once a member, you may provide additional information in the profile section, including but not limited to your bio, your location, as well as your personal web site, if you have one. Providing additional information beyond what is required at registration is entirely optional, but enables you to better identify yourself and find new friends and opportunities in the BuzzBox system. If you contact us by email through the Site, we may keep a record of your contact information and correspondence, and may use your email address, and any information that you provide to us in your message, to respond to you.

Use of Contact Information In addition, we may use your contact information to market to you, and provide you with information about, our products and services, including but not limited to our Service. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such information or communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications.

Log Data When you visit the Site, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website (“Log Data” ). This Log Data may include information such as your IP address, browser type or the domain from which you are visiting, the web-pages you visit, the search terms you use, and any advertisements on which you click. For most users accessing the Internet from an Internet service provider the IP address will be different every time you log on. We use Log Data to monitor the use of the Site and of our Service, and for the Site”™s technical administration. We do not associate your IP address with any other personally identifiable information to identify you personally, except in case of violation of the Terms of Service  
Cookies

Like many websites, we also use “cookie” technology to collect additional website usage data and to improve the Site and our service. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer”™s hard disk. We do not use cookies to collect personally identifiable information. BuzzBox may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with the Site and our Service, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on the Site, and to improve the Site and our services. A session cookie enables certain features of the Site and our service and is deleted from your computer when you disconnect from or leave the Site. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit.  
Information Sharing and Disclosure

Service Providers We engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to us, including, without limitation, hosting and maintenance, customer relationship, database storage and management, and direct marketing campaigns. We will share your personally identifiable information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services, and only pursuant to binding contractual obligations requiring such third parties to maintain the privacy and security of your data.

Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement BuzzBox cooperates with government and law enforcement officials or private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We may disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims, legal process (including subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of BuzzBox or a third party, the safety of the public or any person, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity, or to comply with the law.

Business Transfers BuzzBox may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including your personally identifiable information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy. You will have the opportunity to opt out of any such transfer if the new entity’s planned processing of your information differs materially from that set forth in this Privacy Policy.  
Changing or Deleting Information

If you are a registered user of the Site, you may access and update or correct the information you provided to us by e-mailing us at privacy at buzzbox dot com.  
Security

BuzzBox is very concerned about safeguarding the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information. We employ administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access.

We will make any legally-required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored personal data to you via email or conspicuous posting on this Site in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, consistent with (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system.  
Links to Other Websites

Our Site contains links to other websites. The fact that we link to a website is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personally identifiable information from you. Other sites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personally identifiable information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit.  
Our Policy Towards Children

The Site is not directed to persons under 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with personally identifiable information without their consent, he or she should contact us at privacy at buzzbox dot com. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal identifiable Information, we will delete such information from our files.
